

## José Daniel Camacho

SYSTEMS ENGINEER | FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

CONTACT

☑ j.d.camacho27@gmail.com



MY LINKS

JDcamacho13

in jdcamacho13

ø jd-camachoportafolio.vercel.app

mnf.red/jdcamacho

#### Languages

Spanish



**English** 



#### Introduction

Hill i'm José Daniel Camacho, i have been programming for 3 years, studying web technologies like JavaScript and React and backend development with python. I consider myself hard-working and empathic with mi coworkers and I'm good at identifying problems. I start to work as freelancer in 2021 when i make some landig page's and collaborate in the development of some web apps for a small business, today i'm full stack developer in XT Online Software.

### My skills



Adaptability to change



Continuous learning



Team player

#### My best practices

I try to apply TDD as much as I can. I find it important to write well-documented code, either because it is descriptive or because it explained what I was looking for in relation to the functionality I was looking to implement.

#### **Technologies and tools**

#### **I MASTER**

Express / Tailwind / NextJS / PHP / Django / NodeJS / CSS / StyledComponents / C# / Flask / React / NoSQL / Python / HTML / TypeScript / GraphQL / MySQL / .NET / MongoDB

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE/CAREER



XT Online Software

Full Stack Developer
 Feb 2023 — TODAY (3 months)

TECHNOLOGIES AND TOOLS

JavaScript / .NET / SQL / jQuery



Freelancer developer
 Dec 2021 — Apr 2022 (5 months)

**TECHNOLOGIES AND TOOLS** 

PHP / NodeJS / React / CSS



# Tu gestión empresarial

Freelancer developer
 Oct 2021 — Dec 2021 (3 months)

TECHNOLOGIES AND TOOLS
PHP / HTML / CSS

# EDUCATION/**DEGREES**

#### **Degrees**



### Universidad Bicentenaria de Aragua (UBA)

Sistems engineer
 Sep 2017 — Mar 2022 (4 yrs. and 7 months)

**TECHNOLOGIES AND TOOLS** 

PHP / JavaScript / C++ / Figma / Autocad

#### **Certificates**



#### Node.js: Base de Datos con MongoDB y WebSockets

Issued by: Platzi

Sep 2021 — TODAY (1 year and 8 months)



#### Curso de ECMAScript 6+

Issued by: Platzi

Aug 2021 — TODAY (1 year and 9 months)



#### Curso Práctico de Maquetación en CSS

Issued by: Platzi

Aug 2021 — TODAY (1 year and 9 months)



#### Curso de React Avanzado

Issued by: Platzi

Jul 2021 — TODAY (1 year and 10 months)



#### Curso de Webpack

Issued by: Platzi

Jul 2021 — TODAY (1 year and 10 months)



1 more certificates on my online profile



## **BUT WAIT...**

#### THERE'S EVEN MORE IN MY PROFILE.

This is a short version of my profile, but a longer one is available where you can see more interesting and relevant data.



+ Click here or scan the QR code